skyplanners.com 2017-03-20

# Sky Planners

The SkyPlanners.com is committed to protecting your privacy and safe online experience. This statement of privacy policy applies to the SkyPlanners.com website and governs data collection and usage.

**COLLECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION:  **

  * The SkyPlanners.com collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail id, address, name, home, or work address or telephone number, etc so as to ensure a valid transaction between you and supplier.
  * Please note that we review our Privacy Policy from time to time, and we may make periodic changes to the policy. Therefore, you are advised to periodically review this page to make sure you have the latest version.
  * Any material changes in the way SkyPlanners.com uses personal information will be described in future versions of this Privacy Policy. 

**USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION:**

SkyPlanners.com uses the personal information for following purposes,

**Registration Information:**

You are required to provide your personal details like your name, address, and contact details etc. at the time of registration for SkyPlanners.com services.       The registration information provided by you at the time of registration is maintained confidential and is not disclosed to any third party except as under law.

  1. If you choose to become a registered member of SkyPlanners.com Site, you must provide your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, a unique login name, password and password validation. This information is collected on the registration form for several reasons including but not limited to: 
    1. Personal identification
    2. To complete air, hotel, car, and other reservations
    3. To allow us to contact you for customer service purposes, if necessary
    4. To customize the content of our site to strive to meet your specific needs  
 
  2. You agree to provide authentic and true information. SkyPlanners.com reserves the right to confirm and validate the information and other details provided by you at any point of time. When you sign up for SkyPlanners.com services you will be sent a confirmation mail with your password. Your account will be activated when you access the account with your password provided by SkyPlanners.com. You are responsible for use of your account and password. SkyPlanners.com does not share your account details with any third party without your consent.

**Booking of Offer/Deal:**

In order to book an offer/deal, and/or other services through our site, you must provide us with certain personal information such as your name, credit card number and expiration date, credit card billing address, telephone number, e-mail address and the name or names of the person(s) traveling (if not you). We may also ask you for other personal information, such as your frequent traveler numbers. We require this information to process, fulfill and confirm your reservations and transactions and keep you informed of each transaction's status. If you are making a reservation for one or more travelers other than yourself, you must confirm that each of these other travelers has agreed, in advance, that you may disclose their personal information to us.

  * When you make a booking through SkyPlanners.com, we are required to provide some of your personal information to the airline, hotel, car-rental agency, travel agency or other involved third party to enable the successful fulfillment of your travel arrangements. However, we do not sell or rent individual customer names or other personal information to third parties.

**SHARING AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

From time to time, we may disclose your Personal Information as follows:

  * To those travel service providers with which you make arrangements through our Site, for example, airlines, car rental, hotel, ground transportation, theatere, attraction, or travel insurance. We provide them with the Personal Information needed to make and complete the booking or reservation.
  * To organizations/companies that perform services for or on behalf of SkyPlanners.com, for example to provide customer service, deliver tickets, ship items, process credit cards, for research, marketing, data processing, to measure the use of our Site, to facilitate usage by a visitor, or to offer credit card services or evaluate your creditworthiness. We will share with these companies only that Personal Information which they need to work on our behalf. Some of these service providers may be located in other countries. Your personal information will be provided to these organizations only if they agree to use such information solely for the purpose of providing services to SkyPlanners.com, and under the instructions of SkyPlanners.com, and with respect to that information, to act in a manner consistent with the relevant principles articulated in this Policy.
  * We may collaborate with other companies to offer you additional Products or Services, for example, through promotions. We will share Personal Information that is necessary for these other companies to provide the products or services that you have requested.
  * You agree to provide correct and valid credit card information for the purpose of valid booking transactions on SkyPlanners.com. Your credit card detail is collected by way of secured servers  to ensure protection of your credit card information and security of transaction. Your credit card information shall not be disclosed to any third party except when required under law and shall not be used apart from the financial transaction made by you at SkyPlanners.com. Please refer to our security policy for more details.

**SUBSCRIPTION INFORMATION:**

  * You can avail Newsletter services for Top deals of SkyPlanners.com or alerts on deals of your choice by subscribing to newsletters or alerts by way of your email address. Your email address is used for subscription purpose only and is not disclosed or used for any other purpose than the service subscribed.

**COOKIES POLICY:**

  * What is a cookie?

  1. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes a unique identifier that is sent to your computer or mobile phone (referred to here as a "device") browser from a website's computer and is stored on your devices hard drive.
  2. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser preferences allow it, but to protect your privacy.
  3. Your browser only permits a website to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other websites
  4. Cookies record information about your online preferences and allow us to tailor the websites to your interests. Users have the opportunity to set their devices to accept all cookies, to notify them when a cookie is issued or not to receive cookies at any time. The last of these means that certain personalized services cannot then provide to that user and accordingly you may not be able to take full advantage of all of the SkyPlanners.com features. Each browser is different, so check the "help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.
  5. During the course of any visit to SkyPlanners.com, the pages you see, along with a cookie, are downloaded to your device. Many websites do this, because cookies enable website publishers to do useful things like find out whether device and (probably its user) has visited the website before. This is done on a repeat visit by checking to see, and finding, he cookie left here on the last visit.

  * How does the SkyPlanners.com use cookies:

  1. The SkyPlanners.com use of cookies is similar to that of such other sites and reputed online companies
  2. you can rest assured that no personal information about you (e.g. name, address etc) is gathered or stored in the cookie placed by the SkyPlanners.com site, as a result, none can be passed on to any third parties.
  3. A cookie may also be placed by our advertising server. Such cookies are used only for purposes of tracking the effectiveness of advertising served by us on our site and no personal identification is gathered from you by the use of these cookies.
